export default {
  decks: {
    RevengeOfTheSith: {
      name: 'RevengeOfTheSith',
      title: 'Revenge of the Sith',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'How does Anakin survive droid missiles in the opening battle sequence?',
          answer: 'He causes them to fly into each other'
        },
        {
          question: 'How does General Grievous escape Anakin and Obi-Wan?',
          answer: 'He throws an electrostaff through the window'
        },
        {
          question: 'What advice does Yoda give Anakin about premonitions?',
          answer: 'He must let go of what he fears to lose'
        },
        {
          question: 'What do Anakin and Padmé discuss in their apartment?',
          answer: 'Whether the Republic is on the right side of the war'
        },
        {
          question: 'What does Palpatine tell Anakin at the opera house?',
          answer: 'Good is a point of view'
        },
        {
          question: 'What is the name of the varactyl Obi-Wan rides on Utapau?',
          answer: 'Boga'
        },
        {
          question: 'What exact line does Obi-Wan say in this film that he repeats in "A New Hope"?',
          answer: 'Hello there'
        },
        {
          question: 'How does Mace Windu disarm Palpatine?',
          answer: 'Kick to the face'
        },
        {
          question: 'Which Jedi was not killed during Order 66?',
          answer: 'Agen Kolar'
        },
        {
          question: 'What does Obi-Wan tell Padmé during his search for Anakin?',
          answer: 'Anakin has killed younglings'
        },
        {
          question: 'What order does Palpatine give Darth Vader on Mustafar?',
          answer: 'Shut down the droid armies'
        },
        {
          question: 'Which of the following does NOT occur during the battle between Yoda and Darth Sidious?',
          answer: 'Sidious cuts Yoda with his lightsaber'
        },
        {
          question: 'How does Obi-Wan defeat Anakin?',
          answer: 'He gains an elevated position'
        },
        {
          question: 'Where are Luke and Leia born?',
          answer: 'Polis Massa'
        },
        {
          question: 'Who speaks the final line in the film?',
          answer: 'Threepio'
        }
      ]
    },
    TheLastJedi: {
      name: 'TheLastJedi',
      title: 'The Last Jedi',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'The movie opens with Paige Tico and a fleet of bombers sacrificing themselves to destroy a First Order ship. What kind?',
          answer: 'A Dreadnought'
        },
        {
          question: 'Do we ever actually see Chewbacca eat a porg in this film?',
          answer: 'No'
        },
        {
          question: 'Much of The Last Jedi hinges on memories of the night that Ben Solo destroyed Luke Skywalker\'s training school and turned to the Dark Side. How many times do we see this flashback?',
          answer: '3'
        },
        {
          question: 'Yoda is not about to let Luke run away from the past. What does he remind Luke is the greatest teacher?',
          answer: 'Failure'
        },
        {
          question: 'What is the name of the gorgeous, yet dark, gambling planet that Rose and Finn visit?',
          answer: 'Canto Bight'
        },
        {
          question: 'What is the name of the odd race that lives on Ahch-To with Luke and helps keep up the Jedi structures?',
          answer: 'Caretakers'
        },
        {
          question: 'After Leia falls into a coma, a new Vice Admiral takes control of the Resistance. What is her name?',
          answer: 'Holdo'
        },
        {
          question: 'What is the color of Admiral Snoke\'s robe throughout The Last Jedi?',
          answer: 'Gold'
        },
        {
          question: 'The Last Jedi introduces us to Rose Tico. What role does she play in the Resistance?',
          answer: 'Maintenance worker'
        },
        {
          question: 'In The Last Jedi, we meet a new droid, a similar design to BB-8. What is its name?',
          answer: 'BB-9E'
        },
        {
          question: 'Which of these activities does Rey NOT watch Luke doing while following him through his daily routine?',
          answer: 'Reading the Jedi texts'
        }
      ]
    }
  }
}
